This series looks at life
in one of Britain's busiest airports
On today's show. FlyLo owner Omar Baba
takes on his rivals...
British Airways. you are.
the son of a whore. I spit on you!
...Fearghal's flight hits turbulence..
Is that your wee sick bag?
OK. thanks for that..
Someone had lasagne. didn't they?
Has trouble at Customs
Good morning. good morning..
- It's 8am
And airline owner Omar Baba is launching
an unbelievable transatlantic deal
Today. I announce. the launch.
of the FlyLo 1 flight to New York!
Yes. you heard. I correct!.
1 to New York City.
(UNDER HIS BREATH
With a small booking fee of 480
In an effort to make his service
more attractive to business passengers.
Omar is introducing brand-new flat beds
across his entire fleet.
OK. it looks like the normal seat.
But is a flat bed.
at the press of the button.
Well...good night.
Wake me up when we get to Birmingham.
(SNORES)
The early morning Our Lady Air flight
from Cork has hit turbulence...
But cabin crew member Fearghal is quick
to reassure his passengers.
Hello. is your name Holly?
Your mammy tells me you've been feeling
a wee bit scared. is that right?
Yeah. she just gets a bit frightened.
especially with all the turbulence
Oh. you don't need to worry about that.
That's just like a wee pocket of air.
Like driving along a bumpy road.
-You see?
- Yeah.
I've got somebody who's going to look.
after you. Would you like to meet him?
Yeah?
I'd like to be your best friend.
- Aw... Say thank you.
- Thank you..
35 euro.
Next. please
Meanwhile. over at the FlyLo check-in
Melody is faced with a common problem
Oh. I'm sorry. madam. Your case is
too heavy to go in the hold. madam.
I have to ask you. madam. to remove.
some items from the case. please. madam
Madam.
- How's that now?
- Still over. I'm afraid. madam
MELODY: All we hear from passengers
Is that they don't like
the new baggage allowance rules.
But honestly. what do you really need
to take on holiday. anyway?
Some Hawaiian Tropic
a couple of pairs of bikini bottoms
And a pregnancy-testing 1 kit.
It's still too heavy.
- How much over is it?
- Five kilos. New FlyLo rules.
New baggage allowance is outlined.
very clearly on the FlyLo website. madam
Was just about to tell the lady that!
What my colleague should have
informed you. madam.
Is that it does state very clearly
on the FlyLo website
That before you travel. you do need.
to check the FlyLo website. madam.
I didn't realise
-Www FlyLo.co.uk..
- Right.
Then .com again. It's very simple
www.FlyLo.co.uk.com.org.net.com.com.
- Yes. thank you. Keeley..
- Always happy to help. Melody.
Still over. I'm afraid.
Ah! That's fine now. madam.
Have a good flight..
Next. please
Since they've both been up
for the job of Check-in Manager.
Tensions have arisen
between the two best friends.
If I get promoted as Check-in Manager...
Well. whenl get promoted
as Check-in Manager.
I'm going to use the extra money
to have a breast enhancement.
I actually had mine done
when I was 12.
I could only afford to get one done.
so I had this one done at Christmas.
Went from a D to an F.
But if I get promoted
I'm going to have this one done as well
Yeah. see if you can do a deal
with the surgeon.
Get him to do your face
at the same time
On the other side of the airport
FlyLo employee Taaj has just been told
of a serious plane malfunction.
What happened was. was we was just
getting the plane out of the hangar
And the wing fell off.
So they've got to stick the wing
back on the plane.
But they've got to get themselves.
some special aeroplane glue. isn't it?
So there's going to be
a little bit of a delay.
But thing. 1 IS
I don't want to tell passengers this
Because it might make them
tiny bit nervous.
So I've just been thinking of other things
that I can tell them instead
Excuse me?
- Yes. boss?.
- What's the delay?
Um. a volcano has erupted in Bradford
and is spewing out all ash and that
We've had a phone call from a woman
who lives near the airport.
And she's having a barbecue today.
And she says. please can we have no planes
flying overhead because it's a bit noisy.
We've run out of Appletise
so it's not safe to travel.
The pilot parked the plane
and he can't remember where he left it.
One of the stewards has got eczema
so it would be a bit risky. isn't it?
It's dark and the pilot is worried about
flying the plane at night
In case he can't see anything
- Oh. really?
- Yeah. really!
How would you like
to fly a plane at night?
The pilot's still a at home
cos he's watching Avatar on DVD
And he didn't realise how long it was.
One of the stewards is a batty boy
and he's just found out
That his boyfriend's been
bumming someone else
And he's just like crying and crying
- So we can't fly.
- But that's ridiculous
Want a full refund.
Yeah. but we cannot give a refund
because it is an act of God. isn't it?
How is that an act of God?
God made him batty.
Mickey and Buster.
the airport's paparazzi.
Have just received a tip-off
That a very important passenger
is about to touch down..
Her Majesty the Queen..
- Yeah. love the Queen.
- Love the old Queen.
Thing about the Queen is. she's done
nothing but good for this country.
And when you see her on a postage stamp
you can't help thinking.
"Oh! She's a fine looking woman.
Well. I would.
I would an' all. In fact..
I'd take a photo of you doing it.
That's very kind of you..
Be lovely to have a memento.
Yeah. I'm a traditional royalist
you know what I mean?
When the National Anthem gets played.
I'm always first on my feet. Yeah..
# God save our gracious dum
Long live our noble dum.
# Dum dum dum Queen
# Land of hope and dum dum.
# Rule Bri-dum dum
Britannia rules the dum... #
- (PHONE RINGS)
- Oh. hold up. what's going I on?
- Who is it?
- Hello.
Who is it?
- Oh. you're joking
- Who's joking?
- Oh. you're having a laugh!
- Who's having a laugh?
The Queen has got straight off her plane
into her Daimler..
She's halfway round the M25.
We're not going to get a picture now.
She's gone right up herself.
I can't help thinking this whole
Queen thing has gone to her head
Cow.
All we was going to do
was get a nice little shot of her.
Crown on her head. corgi either side
Showing a nice of bit of cleavage...
Boom. 50 quid from the Daily Star.
And if she's showing a bit of leg
as well.
We could flog it to Nuts Magazine.
- But no.
- No.
She's forgetting the fans. People like us
who put her where she is today..
All these celebrities.
they complain about the paparazzi
- But it's a two-way. street. innit?.
- Yeah. it's a two-way street.
Would she still be Queen
if we didn't photograph her?
Yeah.
- Yeah. I suppose she would. yeah...
- She's the Queen. after all.
-- She's the Queen. yeah.
- Yeah.
Yeah... (MUMBLES)
Ian Foot is the airport's
Chief Immigration Officer.
His job is to prevent illegal immigrants
from entering the UK..
Working in Immigration.
You do sometimes get labelled
with the racism tag..
I do take my job very seriously.
but I'm not in any way racist.
In fact. one of my best friends
is friends with a man who's black.
And he's very black. (WHISTLES)
Oh. yeah. Man. he's black. yeah.
Earlier today. Ian stopped a passenger
at Passport Control.
Whom he believes is trying to gain
unlawful access into the country.
(SLOW AND DELIBERATE) Do you understand
Why I have brought you here?
No. I don't.
Well. it's clear to me
that you've got a forged passport.
- No. I haven't!
- Oh. it's a forgery. all right.
A very good one. I'll grant you that.
But. er. there is one slight giveaway.
- And what is that?!.
There is no such country as Liberia.
Yes. there is. it's in Africa
Oh. in Africa. you say.
It's on a map
Look on a map.
All right. I will look on a map.
Yeah. I think I'm going to enjoy this.
Right...
Liberia. you say?
- Yes.
- Chris!
We've got a new one. Chris. Liberia.
Africa. Africa. Africa... Right. OK.
So. Mrs Mbutu.
Would you be so kind as to point out
The location of this so-called "Liberia"?
There
Oh. yes.
Just hidden underneath Sierra Leone.
What I'm going to do is..
I'm going to let you in this time.
But I would advise you. in future
to travel with a large atlas or globe
So you can prove to people you haven't
made up your country. Good day.
This is disgraceful!
Right.
- You are a very ignorant man.
- All right..
I am disgusted by the way.
that I have been treated.
- OK.
- May I leave now?!
Yes.
You have insulted.
the people of my country.
Yeah.
I'm actually on my lunch break now.
So anything else you say
doesn't really / count.
Oh...!
Don't know what rattled her cage
People come from far and wide
to work at the airport..
Tommy is obsessed with planes
And it's always been his dream
to work in the aviation industry.
I really. really want to be a pilot.
But I found out that you have to
have passed lots of exam...ex...
Tests to be one..
So what I've decided to do instead
Is to get myself a job at the airport
and then work my way up to being a pilot.
Er. cheeseburger.
Press cheeseburger.
Large chocolate milkshake
Press large chocolate milkshake
Chicken nuggets
Press chicken nuggets
Two apple pies
Press apple pie.
Press it again.
I found it quite complicated.
But now that I've served
my first customer.
I think I'm definitely on my way
to becoming a pilot.
Now ask. "Would you like
fries with that?".
- Would you like fries with that?
- Yeah. not me. Him.
So next time you're on a plane.
listen out
Because
you might just hear a voice saying.
"Ladies and gentlemen
welcome on board
"This is Captain Tommy speaking
"Would you like fries with that?"
Meanwhile. there have been reports
of a serious incident in duty free.
And the police are on site
within minutes.
We've had reports of a gentleman
who's very drunk.
And has been abusive
to members of staff.
I'll have a can of whisky..
I tell you what. give us a kiss.
It's all right. Thank you. . Margaret.
I'll deal with it.
Can you calm down. please. sir?
I just want one bottle of whisky..
What's the matter? What's the matter?
Drunk
And you've been abusive
to members of staff.
All right. I'll admit I've had a drink.
I've had a drink. I won't fool you.
I've had a drink.
I think I need to escort you
out of the terminal..
I'm not going. Me plane goes.
In half an hour. I'm not going.
We need to get you outside. get some fresh
air inside you and some black coffee.
All right. I'll I go.
I fly better when I've had
a couple of drinks. anyway.
You know what I mean?
Oh. I'll be all right. once I get
up there. I'll open the window.
The Our Lady Air flight to Dublin
is boarding
Morning
And Fearghal is breaking in
a new steward.
Morning
I'm really excited about today
as it goes.
Cos I just qualified as a steward
and this is my first-ever flight.
And. you know. being a steward
is great. you know -
The money's not bad.
you get to travel a lot
And. er. meet loads of birds. All right
(CHUCKLES)
Lasagne or coq au vin?
Hah... I had coq au vin last night.
- Oh. right?
Yeah. my friend's just bought a Transit.
Lasagne or coq au vin?
I might be wrong. but I've got a feeling
That the guy I'm working with
could be gay..
Get you!
I ain't got nothing against 'em.
but I'm not one meself.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going
to subtly mention that I'm straight
And. er. hope he gets the message.
Any duty free for you today?
(GRUFFLY) Any duty free for you today?
- Any duty free for you today?
Any duty free for you today?
Yes. some Chanel No5. please
Oh. certainly. madam. there you go.
That's what my girlfriend likes.
- Oh. right?
- Yeah. I buy it for me girlfriend
Cos me girlfriend likes it.
cos I really love my girlfriend
Great.
Girlfriend!
I don't know what it is about Lee..
but I'm getting quite a gay vibe from him
Mind you. you. know what they say.
What's the difference between
a straight man and a bisexual?.
Two pints of lager.
- Another pint of lager?
- Yeah. all right..
Before their return flight tomorrow.
Lee and Fearghal have been booked
into a hotel in Dublin..
- Bottoms up.
- Ain't you drinking?
No. I like to stay in control.
# You raise me up
# So I can stand on mountains
# To walk on stormy sea... #
It's 8am. and back at the airport
Coffee kiosk employee Precious
is faced with the morning rush..
Come on! Shoo!
...but she's having to close early.
Problem today. we got no paper cup.
We got coffee. we got milk. we got water.
we got tire. we got sugar.
We got sweetener. we got chocolate
sprinkle. but we got no paper cup.
But to spend the rest of the day
Playing on the fruit machines.
with the petty cash from the till
Praise the Lord for the 30 jackpot.
Closed. Oh. don't worry. me going to
give all me winnings to the church.
On the third day He rose again.
Hallelujah!
# Kumbaya my Lord
Kumbaya
# Kumbaya
# Kumbaya my Lord
Kumbaya
# Oh Lord. Kumbaya. #
Over at the check-in desks.
Melody and Keeley are hard at work.
MELODY: To be honest
I really took this job
Because wanted to travel.
I felt I needed to broaden my horizons
And this year
I've already flown to Birmingham
Manchester and had a week in Luton.
Since the opportunity for promotion
has arisen.
Keeley has been keeping a close eye
- On her friend's performance
- Thank you.
Melody. you. didn't ask.
the security questions.
Oh. sorry. sir. I forgot to ask you
the security questions..
OK.
- Did you pack the case yourself?
- No.
Could anyone have interfered with
your luggage at any point?
Yes.
Did anyone ask you to bring
anything onto the aircraft?
Yes.
Does your bag contain any. lighters.
aerosols or any sharp objects?
Yes. all of those
Good. Enjoy the flight.
Yes. I think what happened earlier
with the security questions
Does show that whichever one of us
does get Helen's job..
It's probably. better
if it's someone with experience
I think. experience is important
but I know..
In my short time at the company..
I have already made a big impact.
I don't know if you've seen this.
This is the FlyLo Hotties calendar
that was s brought out last year..
Omar Baba personally selected
All the sexiest girls.
who work for the airline
And I was actually Miss October.
You weren't asked to do that.
were you. Keeley?.
No. I wasn't. Melody. but then. you see
I probably wouldn't get involved
With something like that.
because I think it's quite down market
You posted that video of you
and your boyfriend on YouPorn.
That was artistic.
Simon and Jackie Trent are Britain's
first husband and wife pilot team..
Five years ago. Simon had an affair.
But the couple are keen
to put the incident behind them
Having re-trained as a pilot
Jackie now accompanies Simon
on all his flights.
Yeah. well. obviously
it can be stressful.
You live together. you work together.
I don't find it stressful.
What I'm saying is. you know..
sometimes there is that danger
That you've had a row at home
and you bring. it into. work.
Nah. Not a problem for me
AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL: Swiftbird.
240 degrees to intercept the ILS.
Swiftbird.
Swiftbird. When established
clear to descend on the ILS
Runway 2-7. right.
Report at 4 Delta.
Clear to descend on the ILS.
Swiftbird.
Can I just say
you've got a really lovely voice?
Er. thank you.
Yeah. you've just got
really lovely velvety tones.
Thanks.
I'm First. Officer Jackie Trent
by the way..
Er. I'm Nigel Stowe
Nice to speak to you. Jackie. Out.
Are you on Facebook?
- Repeat that.. Over.
- Are you on Facebook? Over.
Jackie...
I just really want to see
what you look like.
Er. for the record. I'm tall
I've got black hair and a moustache
You sound hot. Over.
Jackie. we've begun our descent..
I need you to concentrate.
Oh. excuse me. Simon! I'm not the one
who screwed someone else!
Just to say
you're clear for final approach
Thank you.
- Did you Sky+ Strictly?
-Yes.
Back in the terminal. Taaj is helping
FlyLo passengers check in.
- As quickly as possible.
- Is you travelling with hand luggage?
Is you travelling.
with just hand luggage?
Is you travelling with just hand luggage?
- Is you travelling with hand luggage?
- No.
Is you travelling with just hand luggage?.
Is you travelling with just hand luggage?
- Yes.
- You is?
OK. come with me. madam
because we can now check you in
- Electrono-logically. isn't it?
- Oh. right.
But I do need to make sure
That your bag fits into.
the overhead locker. though. isn't it?
Well. it's not going
to fit in there. is it?
Oh. Oh. no. Well. you'd better join
the back of the queue. then. isn't it?.
This is ridiculous!.
You couldn't get anything in there.
No. I know. Me and my mates
was mucking about last night.
I couldn't even get me cock in it.
Moses looks after first and business class
passengers for Great British Air..
He's just been alerted
that there's a very nervous flyer on board
This flight to Budapest.
which is ready for takeoff.
- Are you my frightened lady?
- Yes.
Do you mind if I just perch
my little bottom down here?
Have you been offered
a small glass of fresh orange juice
And a complimentary browse
of the Daily Mail?
Yes. thank you.
OK. my love.
Now. I'm going to give you
a few facts about flight safety
Just to put your mind at rest.
If you'll pardon the pun?.
Please
Do you know how many planes
actually went down last year?
I don't know.
Have a guess
I don't really want to think about it.
Go on.
Five?
More than that.
Ten?
50?
A lot more than that.
150?
- Little bit less.
- 140?
122.
That's all.
And do you know how many planes
were lost at sea last year?.
I don't know.
Nine. OK. this is a fun one
No. thank you..
I don't want to do this any more.
No. no. no. This is a nice one.
Do you know how many planes
Were accidentally shot down
in military. exercises?
Wouldn't want to think about that
Four. OK?
So I hope those little facts
have put your mind at rest.
Happy flighting.(. (CHUCKLES)
PILOT: Ladies and gentleman.
if you could just make sure
Your seat belts are fastened as we've just
been given clearance for takeoff..
Budget airline FlyLo have recently
started selling holidays
Judith and Peter were among the first.
customers to enjoy a FlyLo cruise
We would like to make..
a formal complaint. please.
-Excuse me. Peter.
- Sorry. Judith..
We'd like to make
a formal complaint. please
We have had the cruise from hell!
- When we boarded...
- Peter!
Sorry. Judith.
When we boarded the FlyLo cruise liner.
We were shown to our quarters
In the bowels of the ship
only to discover
That our cabin was flooded
waist-deep with. seawater.
But we thought
"Ho hum. let's get on with it.
"It's only our bottom halves
that are going to get wet."
- So we set sail..
- Peter. I'm talking
- It's very rude.
- Sorry. Judith.
So we set sail and we'd only just left
the port at Athens when it emerged
That all 780 passengers on board.
the vessel had contracted dysentery.
You had to queue for 14 hours...
Peter. you and I are going.
to come to blows in a minute
You had to queue for 14 hours
to use the lavatories.
Well. we'd been waiting 13 hours
and it was very nearly our turn
When we heard gunshots and discovered
that the boat had been boarded by pirates
- They rounded up all the passengers..
- Peter!
They rounded up all the passengers.
on deck and singled out Peter and I
And took us hostage..
which meant we missed the buffet.
We were then taken to a room
and told that one of us
Was going to have to perform sexual acts
upon the pirates at gunpoint.
Well. I popped my hand in the air
and volunteered Peter..
But before my husband had a chance
To engage in anything other than.
mild foreplay with three of the men.
The boat was stormed
by the Greek coastguard
There was a shoot-out. bodies everywhere
and just as I thought..
"Surely this cruise
can't get any worse
We discovered that the cabaret
that night was John Barrowman.
That's when I broke down
It's 4pm
and although it's been several hours
Since Precious was forced to close
the coffee kiosk
She's still at the airport.
Oh. a very bad thing just happened
Was playing on me
Deal Or No Deal fruit machine.
You know the television show
With that nice Christian boy
Noel Edmonson?
Well. the Devil must've got inside Noel
Cos he just thieved
180 of the petty cash from me.
But don't worry. because
I'm going to win all the money back.
Have you got change of a 10 note?
Quick as you can. my love
I don't have 10. I've only got 5.
There's a place for you in Heaven.
Hey! Get away from that fruit machine!
I've got my money in there!.
Gambling is the Devil's work.
Come on. Noel.
Our Lady Air cabin crew
Fearghal and Lee
Are working the return flight from Dublin
Croissant or muesli?
- Croissant or muesli?
What happened last night.
was very much a one-off.
I've told Fearghal that.
I think just cos you have sex
with a guy don't make you a gay.
Lee certainly knows
how to please a man.
It was mind-blowing. He threw me
round the room. like a rag doll.
It was the most intense. animalistic.
erotic encounter of my life.
Hope me girlfriend don't see this.
David Schwimmer has been stopped
and searched at Customs..
The Friends star
was attempting to smuggle
A large number of illegal items
into the country..
One copy Chicks With Dicks
One copy She-Male Orgy.
- One copy Tranny Mania.
- Tranny Mania.
One copy. She-Male Orgy 3.
One copy Ladyboy Lick Fest
Final item - one copy
My Daughter Has A Dick.
Right. You're. aware
these items are. illegal in the UK.
-(HE : mouths)
- In which case
Would you care to explain why you have
attempted to bring them into the country?.
Well. this is very...
It's very. difficult for me
Because I don't want to get
someone else in trouble...
But...
...they're actually.
a present for...a friend
- Which friend?
Matt LeBlanc.
Matt LeBlanc?
That's correct.
It...it's sad. but. um.
He really can only become aroused.
when watching this sort of material.
Have you watched any of these films?
I have
and I found it absolutely disgusting
Which of the. DVDs did you watch.
Mr Schwimmer?
All of them. All of... All of them.
Was very curious
As to what kind of films.
Matt had asked me to buy for him.
- Really?!
- Mm-hm.
You know. the stories actually
do kind of drag you in.
You know. will the pool get cleaned?
You do realise we have no option
but to confiscate these items?
Yeah. I do. I do. And actually I'm glad..
because when Matt sees this on...on TV
He will understand that what he asked
me to do is utterly unacceptable.
In fact. can I...can I just address
the camera for a second?
Matt. this is your friend.
David Schwimmer.
You've got a problem. buddy.
And I'm...
Mean you... Look. you're sick
and you need help
And I will do everything within
my power to help you get help.
Thank you.
Thank you all. This...
An excellent job here
And I really appreciate it.
- Sit down. sir.
- They're for Jennifer Aniston.
And so another eventful day
at the airport draws to a close
(MUMBLED SHOUTS)
Captain Stirick had a strong coffee
and flew the Airbus to. Vienna.
(SHOUTS ; CONTINUE)
Omar's flat-bed scheme
went down like a cup of cold sick.
And David Schwimmer was a admitted
to a clinic in Arizona.
To treat his addiction
to transsexual pornography